Guide to the Washington Theater Club records, 1952-1983 MS2061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Production files, 1960-1979; MS2061 Series 1
  - Production 30--flyers and brochures, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Production 30--promotion - administrative, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Production 30--production staff worksheets, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Production 30--opening night lists, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Production 30--art work, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Production 31, The Knack, Ann Jellicoe. --programs., 1966 October 13-November 06 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Production 31--newspaper and magazine, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Production 31--advertisements, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Production 31--news releases, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Production 31--flyers and brochures, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Production 31--promotion - administrative, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Production 31--art work, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Production 32, The Lover, Harold Pinter, and Hughie, Eugene O'Neill. --programs, 1966 November 10-December 04 (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Production 32--newspaper and magazine, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Production 32--advertisement, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Production 32--news releases, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Production 32--promotion - administrative, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - Production 32--production staff worksheets, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Production 32--art work, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 208)
  - Production 33, The Fantasticks, Tom Jones and Harvey Schmidt. --programs, 1966 December 08-1967 January 15 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Production 33--newspaper and magazine, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - Production 33--advertisements, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Production 33--news releases, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - Production 33--flyers and brochures, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Production 33--promotion - administrative, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Production 33--production staff worksheets, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Production 33--art work, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Production 34, Tiny Alice, Edward Albee. --programs., 1967 January 19-February 12 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Production 34--newspaper and magazine, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Production 34--advertisements, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Production 34--news releases, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Production 34--flyers and borchures, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Production 34--promotion - administrative, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Production 34--art work, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Production 35, The Marriage of Mr. Mississippi, Friedrich Duerrenmatt.--programs, 1967 February 16-March 12 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Production 35--newspaper and magazine, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Production 35--advertisements, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Production 35--news releases, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Production 35--flyers and brochures, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Production 35--promotion - administrative, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Production 35--art work, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Production 36, The Killer, Eugene lonesco. --programs., 1967 March 16-April 09 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Production 36--newspaper and magazines, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Production 36--advertisements, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Production 36--news releases, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Production 36--flyers and brochures, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Production 36--promotion - administrative, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Production 36--art work, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Production 37, The Waters of Babylon, John Arden. --programs, 1967 April 13-May 07 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Production 37--newspaper and magazine, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Production 37--advertisements, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Production 37--news releases, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Production 37--promotion - administrative, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Production 37--production staff worksheets, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Production 37--art work, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Production 38, Son of Spread Eagle, a topical revue. --programs, 1967 May 11-June 04 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Production 38--newspaper and magazine, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Production 38--advertisements, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Production 38--news releases, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Production 38--flyers and brochures, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Production 38--promotion - administrative, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Production 38--WTC extended, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Production 38--production staff worksheets, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Production 38--opening night lists, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Production 38--art work, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Production 39, Luv, Murray Schisgal.--programs, 1967 July 28-August 28 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Production 39--newspaper and magazines, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Production 39--advertisements, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Production 39--news releases, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Production 39--art work, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Production 40, My Sweet Charlie, David Westheimer --programs, 1967 October 12-November 19 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Production 40--newspaper and magazine, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Production 40--advertisements, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Production 40--news releases, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Production 40--flyers and brochures, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Production 40--promotion - administrative, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Production 40--opening night lists, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Production 40--art work, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Production 40--cast background information, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Production 41, Eh?, Henry Livings. --programs, 1967 November 23-December 31 (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Production 41--newspaperand magazine, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Production 41--advertisements, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Production 41--news releases, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Production 41--flyers and brochures, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Production 41--promotion - administrative, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Production 41--art work, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Production 42, No Man's Land, John Wilson. --programs., 1968 January 04-February 11 (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Production 42--newspaper and magazine, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Production 42--advertisements, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Production 42--news releases, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Production 42--flyers and brochures, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Production 42--promotion - administrative, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Production 42--production staff worksheets 2, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Production 42--art work, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Production 43, Caligula, Albert Camus. --programs., 1968 February 15-March 24 (Box 9, Folder 284)
  - Production 43--newspaper and magazine, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 285)
  - Production 43--advertisements, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 286)
  - Production 43--news releases, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 287)
  - Production 43--flyers and brochures, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 288)
  - Production 43--promotion - administrative, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 289)
  - Production 43--opening night lists, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 290)
  - Production 43--art work, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Production 44, Five Evenings, Aleksandr Volodin. --programs., 1968 March 28-May 05 (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Production 44--newspaper and magazine, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 293)
  - Production 44--advertisements, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 294)
  - Production 44--news releases, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Production 44--promotion - administrative, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - Production 44--art work, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 297)
  - Production 45, Green Julia, Paul Ableman, and The Basement, Murray Schisgal. --programs, 1968 May 09-June 16 (Box 9, Folder 298)
  - Production 45--newspaper and magazine, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 299)
  - Production 45--advertisements, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 300)
  - Production 45--news releases, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - Production 45--promotion - administrative, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 302)
  - Production 45--opening night lists, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Production 45--art work, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Production 46, Spread Eagle Strikes Back, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - Production 46--newspaper and magazine, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - Production 46--advertisements, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - Production 46--news releases, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - Production 46--promotion - administrative, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - Production 46--production staff worksheets, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - Production 46--art work, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Production 47, The Gingham Dog, Lanford Wilson.--programs, 1968 September 26-October 27 (Box 10, Folder 312)
  - Production 47--newspaper and magazines, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 313)
  - Production 47--advertisements, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 314)
  - Production 47--news releases, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 315)
  - Production 47--promotion - administrative, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 316)
  - Production 47--art work, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 317)
  - Production 48, The Lion in Winter, James Goldman.--programs, 1968 October 31-December 01 (Box 10, Folder 318)
  - Production 48--newspaper and magazine, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 319)
  - Production 48--advertisements, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Production 48--news releases, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 321)
  - Production 48--promotion - administrative, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 322)
  - Production 48--art work, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 323)
  - Production 49, Lock Up Your Daughters, Lionel Bart, Bernard Miles,and Laurie Johnson. --programs, 1968 December 05-1969 January 05 (Box 10, Folder 324)
  - Production 49--newspaper and magazine, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 325)
  - Production 49--advertisements, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 326)
  - Production 49--news releases, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 327)
  - Production 49--flyers and Brochures, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 328)
  - Production 49--promotion - administrative, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 329)
  - Production 49--production staff worksheets, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 330)
  - Production 49--art work, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 331)
  - Production 50, Mr. Tambo, Mr. Bones, Alexander Panas. --programs., 1969 January 09-February 09 (Box 11, Folder 332)
  - Production 50--newspaper and magazine, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 333)
  - Production 50--advertisements, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 334)
  - Production 50--news releases, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 335)
  - Production 50--promotion - administrative, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 336)
  - Production 50--production staff worksheets, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 337)
  - Production 50--production staff worksheets, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 338)
  - Production 50--production staff worksheets, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 339)
  - Production 50--art work, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 340)
  - Production 51--programs. Who's Happy Now?, Oliver Hailey, 1969 February 13-March 16 (Box 12, Folder 341)
  - Production 51--newspaper and magazine, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 342)
  - Production 51--advertisements, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 343)
  - Production 51--news releases, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 344)
  - Production 51--flyers and brochures, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 345)
  - Production 51--promotion - administrative, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 346)
  - Production 51--production staff worksheets, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 347)
  - Production 51--opening night lists, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 348)
  - Production 51--art work, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 349)
  - Production 52, --programs The Indian Wants the Bronx, Israel Horovitz, And Other Caged Birds, Richard O'Donnell, and Odds and Ends, Milton Wisoff., 1969 March 20-April 20 (Box 12, Folder 350)
  - Production 52--newspaper and magazine, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 351)
  - Production 52--advertisements, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 352)
  - Production 52--news releases, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 353)
  - Production 52--promotion - administrative, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 354)
  - Production 52--production staff worksheets, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 355)
  - Production 52--art work, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 356)
  - Production 53, Bread and Butter, Cecil Taylor, --programs., 1969 April 24-May 25 (Box 12, Folder 357)
  - Production 53--newspaper and magazine, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 358)
  - Production 53--advertisements, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 359)
  - Production 53--news releases, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 360)
  - Production 53--flyers and brochures, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 361)
  - Production 53--promotion - administrative, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - Production 53--art work, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 363)
  - Production 53--cast background information, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 364)
  - Production 54, Spread Eagle IV, 4th Original Revue. --programs, 1969 June 04-August 10 (Box 13, Folder 365)
  - Production 54--newspaper and magazines, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 366)
  - Production 54--advertisements, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 367)
  - Production 54--news releases, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 368)
  - Production 54--flyers and brochures, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 369)
  - Production 54--promotion - administrative, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 370)
  - Production 54--WTC extended, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 371)
  - Production 54--production staff worksheets, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 372)
  - Production 54--art work, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 373)
  - Production 55--programs The Moths, Raffi Arzoomanian, 1969 October 22-1970 January 11 (Box 13, Folder 374)
  - Production 55--newspaper and magazine, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 375)
  - Production 55--advertisements, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 376)
  - Production 55--news releases, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 377)
  - Production 55--flyers and brochures, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 378)
  - Production 55--promotion - administrative, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 379)
  - Production 55--art work, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 380)
  - Production 55--cast background information, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 381)
  - Production 56, --programs The Decline and Fall of the Entire World as Seen Through the Eyes of Cole Porter, Ben Bagley., 1969 December 10-1970 April 12 (Box 14, Folder 382)
  - Production 56--newspaper and magazine, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 383)
  - Production 56--advertisements, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 384)
  - Production 56--news releases, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 385)
  - Production 56--flyers and brochures, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 386)
  - Production 56--promotion - administrative, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 387)
  - Production 56--WTC extended, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 388)
  - Production 56--production staff worksheets, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 389)
  - Production 56--opening night lists, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 390)
  - Production 56--art work, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 391)
  - Production 56--cast background information, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 392)
  - Production 57--programs The Wolves, Robert Koesis, 1970 January 21-February 15 (Box 14, Folder 393)
  - Production 57--newspaper and magazines, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 394)
  - Production 57--advertisements, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 395)
  - Production 57--news releases, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 396)
  - Production 57--flyers and brochures, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 397)
  - Production 57--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 398)
  - Production 57--opening night lists, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 399)
  - Production 57--art work, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 400)
  - Production 58--programs Adventures in the Skin Trade, Andrew Sinclair., 1970 February 25-March 22 (Box 15, Folder 401)
  - Production 58--newspaper and magazine, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 402)
  - Production 58--advertisements, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 403)
  - Production 58--news releases, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 404)
  - Production 58--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 405)
  - Production 58--opening night lists, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 406)
  - Production 58--art work, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 407)
  - Production 59--programs Serenading Louie, Lanford Wilson., 1970 April 01-26 (Box 15, Folder 408)
  - Production 59--newspaper and magazine, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 409)
  - Production 59--advertisements, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 410)
  - Production 59--news releases, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 411)
  - Production 59--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 412)
  - Production 59--opening night lists, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 413)
  - Production 59--art work, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 414)
  - Production 60--programs Continental Divide, Oliver Hailey., 1970 May 06-31 (Box 15, Folder 415)
  - Production 60--newspaper and magazine, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 416)
  - Production 60--advertisements, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 417)
  - Production 60--news releases, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 418)
  - Production 60--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 419)
  - Production 60--opening night lists, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 420)
  - Production 60--art work, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 421)
  - Production 61--programs Exit the King, Eugene Ionesco., 1970 June 10-July 05 (Box 15, Folder 422)
  - Production 61--newspaper and magazine, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 423)
  - Production 61--advertisements, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 424)
  - Production 61--news releases, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 425)
  - Production 61--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 426)
  - Production 61--opening night lists, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 427)
  - Production 61--art work, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 428)
  - Production 62, --programs Before You Go, Lawrence Holofcener., 1970 July 15-August 16 (Box 16, Folder 429)
  - Production 62--newspaper and magazines, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 430)
  - Production 62--advertisements, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 431)
  - Production 62--news releases, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 432)
  - Production 62--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 433)
  - Production 62--WTC extended, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 434)
  - Production 62--production staff worksheets, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 435)
  - Production 62--art work, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 436)
  - Production 63,--programs The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds, Paul Zindel, 1970 September 23-November 01 (Box 16, Folder 437)
  - Production 63--newspaper and magazine, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 438)
  - Production 63--advertisements, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 439)
  - Production 63--news releases, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 440)
  - Production 63--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 441)
  - Production 63--production staff worksheets, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 442)
  - Production 63--opening night lists, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 443)
  - Production 63--art work, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 444)
  - Production 64, --programs The Last Sweet Days of Isaac, Gretchen Cryer and Nancy Ford, 1970 November 11-December 06 (Box 16, Folder 445)
  - Production 64--newspaper and magazine, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 446)
  - Production 64--advertisements, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 447)
  - Production 64--news releases, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 448)
  - Production 64--flyers and brochures, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 449)
  - Production 64--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 450)
  - Production 64--opening night lists, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 451)
  - Production 64--art work, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 452)
  - Production 65--programs, A Fifth of Spread Eagle, 5th Original Revue, 1970 December 16-1971 January 10 (Box 17, Folder 453)
  - Production 65--newspaper and magazine, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 454)
  - Production 65--advertisements, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 455)
  - Production 65--news releases, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 456)
  - Production 65--promotion - administrative, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 457)
  - Production 65--production staff worksheets, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 458)
  - Production 65--opening night lists, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 459)
  - Production 65--art work, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 460)
  - Production 66,--programs Little Boxes - "Coffee Lace" and "Trevor" 2 One Acts, John Bowen, 1971 January 20-February 14 (Box 17, Folder 461)
  - Production 66--newspaper and magazine, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 462)
  - Production 66--advertisements, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 463)
  - Production 66--news releases, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 464)
  - Production 66--promotion - administrative, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 465)
  - Production 66--production staff worksheets, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 466)
  - Production 66--opening night lists, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 467)
  - Production 66--art work, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 468)
  - Production 66--cast background information, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 469)
  - Production 67,--programs The Web and the Rock, Dolores Sutton, 1971 February 24-March 21 (Box 17, Folder 470)
  - Production 67--newspaper and magazine, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 471)
  - Production 67--advertisements, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 472)
  - Production 67--news releases, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 473)
  - Production 67--promotion - administrative, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 474)
  - Production 67--opening night lists, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 475)
  - Production 67--art work, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 476)
  - Production 68, --programs "The Chinese" and "Dr. Fish" - 2 One Acts, Murray Schisgal, 1971 March 31-April 25 (Box 17, Folder 477)
  - Production 68--newspaper and magazine, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 478)
  - Production 68--advertisements, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 479)
  - Production 68--news releases, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 480)
  - Production 68--promotion - administrative, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 481)
  - Production 68--opening night lists, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 482)
  - Production 68--art work, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 483)
  - Production 69,--programs Father's Day, Oliver Hailey, 1971 May 05-30 (Box 18, Folder 484)
  - Production 69--newspaper and magazine, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 485)
  - Production 69--advertisements, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 486)
  - Production 69--news releases, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 487)
  - Production 69--flyers and brochures, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 488)
  - Production 69--promotion - administrative, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 489)
  - Production 69--opening night lists, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 490)
  - Production 69--art work, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 491)
  - Production 70, --programs Whores, Wars, and Tin Pan Alley, Kurt Weill, 1971 June 09-July 04 (Box 18, Folder 492)
  - Production 70--newspaper and magazine, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 493)
  - Production 70--advertisements, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 494)
  - Production 70--news releases, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 495)
  - Production 70--flyers and brochures, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 496)
  - Production 70--promotion - administrative, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 497)
  - Production 70--opening night lists, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 498)
  - Production 70--art work, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 499)
  - Production 71, --programs Adaptation - Next, Elaine May and Terrence McNally, 1971 September 29-October 24 (Box 18, Folder 500)
  - Production 71--newspaper and magazine, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 501)
  - Production 71--advertisements, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 502)
  - Production 71--news releases, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 503)
  - Production 71--flyers and brochures, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 504)
  - Production 71--promotion - administrative, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 505)
  - Production 71--production staff worksheets, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 506)
  - Production 71--opening night lists, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 507)
  - Production 71--art work, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 508)
  - Production 72, --programs All Over, Edward Albee., 1971 November 03-28 (Box 19, Folder 509)
  - Production 72--newspaper and magazine, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Production 72--advertisements, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Production 72--news releases, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - Production 72--promotion - administrative, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 513)
  - Production 72--production staff worksheets, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 514)
  - Production 72--opening night lists, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 515)
  - Production 72--art work, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 516)
  - Production 72--cast background information, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 517)
  - Production 73, --programs Curse You, Spread Eagle, A Topical Revue., 1971 December 08-1972 January 09 (Box 19, Folder 518)
  - Production 73--newspaper and magazine, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 519)
  - Production 73--advertisements, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 520)
  - Production 73--news releases, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 521)